Come out to the coast.
We'll get together.
Have a few laughs.
Mr. McClane.
My friends call me John.
Yeah, we got it.
What are you gonna do?
Improvise!
It's something, huh?
We didn't know whether to
burn it or put it in a museum.
I'm sure that he said the same thing about me.
You coming?
I'm having fun.
I'm awake.
In five years,
you have never apologized to me this quickly.
Something's going on here.
I'm gonna find out what it is.
I don't wanna talk about time travel,
'cause if we start talking about it,
then we're gonna be here
all day talking about it
making diagrams with straws.
Who's chopper is this?
It's Zed's.
Who's Zed?
Zed's dead, baby. Zed's dead.
Look. Have any of you heard
of the Army of the 12 Monkeys?
Why did you leave me?
I didn't leave you.
What?
I better make the hole a little bigger.
Anybody else wanna negotiate?
Until help arrives,
I'm deputizing the little
guy, the skinny one,
and the boy with a patch on his eye
to come with me in the station wagon.
Oh no! Put me back in!
Put me back in please!
Every red-blooded American knows
that the only condiment you are ever
supposed to put on a hamburger is ketchup!
You got a great attitude, Bob.
Real credit to the force, you are.