(gentle music)
- Come on Phil, what is it?
There is something there, right?
- Not if you can't see it, there ain't.
- I was a great one for the
pictures when I was your age.
I used to think you could
climb right inside the screen.
- I wonder why it was stars she gave us?
Why not diamonds, why not art?
Yo no soy Americana.
Yo soy Puertorriqueña.
- It's Auden. Chill of the crooked wing
falls down along my body.
That's just something I
taught them in the crisis.
- I'm here, I've been here
dreaming and believing just like you,
you just don't wanna see me.
- When you're at school you do tenses.
Well here there is only one tense.
There is no future,
past and the present are the same thing.
- Arturo.
(speaking in in a foreign language)
- I'm not telling these people
that I check the wrong bax.
If I'm gonna die.
- You're not.
- I would rather die standing up.
- And how sad is that?
That we as Christians who
are supposed to love everyone
are afraid so badly of an AIDS patient.
- Children are a crushing responsibility.
Happy birthday.
(gentle music)